Guide to the Vera L. Connolly Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Fiction, 1907-1952
  - Subseries III.2: Untitled Drafts and Notes, 1907-circa 1952
    - Dorthea Dix--TV Concept, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Fiction Ideas, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Fiction Plots--Notebook, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Musical Comedy, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Published Short Stories, 1907-1917 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Untitled Drafts, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
    - Verse, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Series IV: General, 1910-1952
  This small series contains a variety of materials, including articles about Connolly, resumes and biographical articles, contracts, and lecture notes from events held by the Association of Students of Dr. Hendrik J. deLange.
  - "Bright Interlude," by Josephine Betham and Gertrude Keck--Post-WWII Readjustment, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - "Family Man," by Ben Barzman, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - The Association of Students of Dr. Hendrik J. deLange--Lecture Notes, 1939, 1942, (3 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
  - Biographical Information
    - Articles about Connolly, 1929-1938 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - College and Canada Trip, 1910-1918 (includes photograph) (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Dossier, circa 1950 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Interview, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Resume, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook, 1929-1950, (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
    - Who's Who in America, 1951-1952 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Publication--Report of Investigation, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Contract between Connolly and Theodora Brogan, 1932 July 25 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Motion Picture Rights, 1917-1920 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Portable File, 1942-1944 (Box 28, Folder 12)